<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skyminer on Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/tags/skyminer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Skyminer on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skycoin.net/blog/tags/skyminer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Hardware Store Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skycoin-hardware-store-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skycoin-hardware-store-launch/</guid>
      <description>The Skycoin Hardware Store has officially launched! Skyfleet members will now have direct access to Skycoin hardware available through our official Skycoin Store.
Official Skyminers Now Available While the amount of Skycoin Miners connected to the Skywire network continuously grows, the Skycoin team has decided to make a second batch of Official Skycoin Miners available during launch.
As of now, Skyminers are available to purchase for existing and new Skyfleet members looking to join the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a DIY Skyminer [INFOGRAPHIC]</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/build-a-diy-skycoin-miner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/build-a-diy-skycoin-miner/</guid>
      <description> To be part of Skywire you can build your own Skyminer. All you need are some skills and the following items:  x1 Mainboard (~$100) x7 Storage (~$12 each) x1 Ethernet LAN Cable (~$10) x1 OS (FREE) x7 Compute Module (~$29 each) x1 Case (~$40) x1 Power Supply (~$16)  Total: ~$450
 Read more about DIY Skyminers here: https://christianott.co/skycoin_pine64miner_en/
Official assembly video tutorial: https://youtu.be/22ytucw2A4k
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyminer Troubleshooting FAQs</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skyminer-troubleshooting-faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skyminer-troubleshooting-faqs/</guid>
      <description>1. Why won&amp;rsquo;t my Orange Pis turn on or light up when I turn on my Skyminer? The Orange Pis will only light up and turn on when you flash the SD cards with the appropriate images and then insert into the Orange Pis.
2. Why won&amp;rsquo;t anything light up or turn on when I turn on the Skyminer? Some switches come with the on/off sides reversed, as compared to instructions in the manual, which expects the &amp;ldquo;on&amp;rdquo; side to be on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Digest: Skyminer… Are you kidding me? [INFOGRAPHIC]</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/what-is-skycoin-skyminer-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/what-is-skycoin-skyminer-mining/</guid>
      <description>A Skyminer? Are you kidding me? No, we are not kidding you. The Skyminer is no joke. It’s an advanced yet robust piece of hardware that we’re distributing all over the world. Built from scratch, this little fella will do amazing things!
 Meticulously built from the highest quality components. Configured to be the backbone of the new decentralized internet, Skywire. Allows operators to earn passive income as it powers the new Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire Testnet FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-testnet-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-testnet-faq/</guid>
      <description>Foreword to the first chapter of a new internet Last Update: April 5, 2018
We know you all have been very eager to learn more about the next milestone of Skycoin, the Skywire testnet. We are proud to say the wait is now over! We have the answers for you below.
Please keep in mind that this will be an evolving FAQ and a living document as we progress through our testnet, so check back here often for updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Digest: Skywire Meshnet Project [INFOGRAPHIC]</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/understanding-the-skywire-meshnet-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/understanding-the-skywire-meshnet-project/</guid>
      <description>1. Skywire objectives:  Increase broadband competition. Provide an alternative to ISPs. Enable communities to build ISPs on user operated infrastructure. Create a global open access mesh network, or &amp;ldquo;meshnet.&amp;rdquo;  2. Skywire is a new privacy protocol.  Low Latency High Performance Privacy Preserving Supports Operation Over Wifi Supports Clearnet Operation  3. Open access and privacy preserving.  Anyone with a client can connect to a Skywire node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire Testnet Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-testnet-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-testnet-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Our esteemed development team is proud to announce that the Skywire testnet is ready for launch ahead of schedule. Skywire is the foundation upon which the Skycoin platform will be built. Skywire&amp;rsquo;s uses range from operating our innovative web-of-trust consensus algorithm, Obelisk, to operating an end-to-end encrypted distributed internet that all Skycoin holders will ultimately gain free access to via the Coin Hour system.
Stay tuned for the official launch date coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Digest: Skywire Overview [INFOGRAPHIC]</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skycoin-digest-skywire-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skycoin-digest-skywire-overview/</guid>
      <description>Skywire – Reinventing the Internet The Skycoin ecosystem has several critical pieces, all beautifully held together by Skywire.
Skywire takes back control from ISPs and puts it into the hands of users. That means no huge Internet bills and no unfair business practices. A self-sufficient network, 100% owned and operated by its users.
Skywire uses peer-to-peer blockchain technology to create a decentralized mesh network that’s fast, private, and secure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Digest: Why do we need a FREE Internet? [INFOGRAPHIC]</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/why-do-we-need-a-free-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/why-do-we-need-a-free-internet/</guid>
      <description>Why are we building a free internet? It’s a long list so we’ll give you our top 3.
1.) Freedom All over the world governments both deny and restrict their citizenries access to the internet as well as censor opposing voices. They have forgotten who they serve.
2.) Privacy Governments &amp;amp; Corporations track and censor everything we do online. Whether it’s to get dirt on a political opponent or sell you the next new batman figurine… It’s wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Net Neutrality Rollback and How Skycoin Can Defeat It</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/the-net-neutrality-rollback-and-how-skycoin-can-defeat-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/the-net-neutrality-rollback-and-how-skycoin-can-defeat-it/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, the FCC instituted net neutrality rules classifying the internet as a public utility. This prevented internet service providers (ISPs) from prioritizing certain websites over others and encouraged a free and open internet where all businesses and individuals could thrive.
Now, under Trump-appointed FCC chairman Ajit Pai, a vote to slash net neutrality protections is looming. Pai was nominated for a second five-year term on October 2 despite widespread outcry over his agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire: The Next Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-the-next-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-the-next-internet/</guid>
      <description>In spring 2017, the FCC made a proposal in which internet service providers can collect, use, and sell information about customer browsing habits. ISPs can do this without permission. Customers can’t opt out. Being a customer of one of these corporations means that you’re paying to be tracked, plain and simple.
With customer tracking, unreliable coverage, high rates, long hold times and poor customer service, ISPs have become some of the most hated companies in America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire Miner: Hardware for the Next Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-miner-hardware-for-the-next-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-miner-hardware-for-the-next-internet/</guid>
      <description>Sign up to our mailing list for Skywire Miner updates: http://eepurl.com/c4DyAv
How can we create a truly free and open internet? To answer this question, we developed Skywire, the new alternative internet. Skywire is a groundbreaking, novel technology that takes control from large internet service providers (ISPs) and gives it back to the users. Its peer-to-peer model promotes net neutrality and sharing of content without blocking, slowdowns, or censorship. Skywire’s open-access network preserves privacy and encourages free speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire: A Free and Open Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-a-free-and-open-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/skywire-a-free-and-open-internet/</guid>
      <description>The internet gives us the illusion of control. We can socialize, consume, and do business instantly through services provided by Google, Facebook, Apple, and Amazon. Seems convenient, right? It is – until you consider what you’re giving up.
We don’t control our lives online. Large companies and internet service providers (ISPs) collect our data, track our movements, and shape our experiences. Every time we use the internet, we give these companies total power over us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #133</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/development-update-133/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/blog/posts/development-update-133/</guid>
      <description>Update:
Comment: Quote from: hannusolo on June 12, 2017, 07:55:31 PM
 Regarding tha subject, how much compute power and memory would these nodes require? I saw the renders on telegram about the proposed hardware node, but I have a mining pc that has a mostly unused cpu and memory, thinking about a little upgrade on this side in the future.
 Response: Many hacking firms, used to take over peoples computers so they could put adware on them or build up a botnet, or do clickfraud to make websites look like they were getting more views than they actually are.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>